<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2026-01-08T11:05:40+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Art Forum Hair</title><subtitle>Art Forum Hair</subtitle><author><name>Albena</name></author><entry><title type="html">REVOLUTION – Flixy hair extensions! Now everything is easier and faster!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/revolution-flixy-hair-extensions-now-everything-is-easier-and-faster/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="REVOLUTION – Flixy hair extensions! Now everything is easier and faster!" /><published>2019-07-24T00:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2019-07-24T00:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/revolution-flixy-hair-extensions-now-everything-is-easier-and-faster</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/revolution-flixy-hair-extensions-now-everything-is-easier-and-faster/"><![CDATA[<p>More and more women of all ages prefer the variety of hair styles that the hair extensions provide. It does not matter if you want to wear hair extension constantly or just to put a ponytail for a special moment in your life. Indeed, flixy hair extensions are the most innovative solution to achieve the volume and length of your hair. Now it is possible for every woman to be a princess with long hair in just a few minutes. Forget about needles, threads, bands, brackets, heat, glue or micro rings.</p>

<p>We spoke to the expert Albena Atanasova, hairdresser and owner of the prestigious hair salon in Sofia, Art Forum. She creates 100% natural human hair extensions which are of high quality to fit perfectly on your natural hair. Albena says that the flixy hair extensions are a revolution in hair extension methods. They are made from natural hair which is connected with a thin cord on both sides. The cord is mixed with your hair and it is completely invisible.</p>

<p>Our next questions to Albena are: “How to put in this hair extension? What are the advantages and disadvantages of the flixy hair extensions?”</p>

<p>- It is extremely easy and you do not need a hairdresser. There are 3 simple steps:</p>

<ol>
  <li>Place your flixy hair extension on your head.</li>
  <li>Use a comb to remove our hair over the thin cord.</li>
  <li>Brush your hair and you are done!</li>
</ol>

<p>Advantages? Flixy hair extensions are placed extremely fast and easy and they are completely harmless to your own hair.</p>

<p>Disadvantages? There are practically none.</p>

<p>In Art Forum solon, you can find a great variety of high quality wavy, straight and curly hair in different colors. Flixy hair extensions are placed quickly and easily and this will save you time and money.</p>

<p>Look forward to our exclusive collection of high-quality products and professional care for your hair!</p>]]></content><author><name>Albena</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[More and more women of all ages prefer the variety of hair styles that the hair extensions provide. It does not matter if you want to wear hair extension constantly or just to put a ponytail for a special moment in your life. Indeed, flixy hair extensions are the most innovative solution to achieve the volume and length of your hair. Now it is possible for every woman to be a princess with long hair in just a few minutes. Forget about needles, threads, bands, brackets, heat, glue or micro rings.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Art Forum’s first training course is a reality! What to еxpect in future!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/art-forums-first-training-course-reality-%D0%B5xpect-future/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Art Forum’s first training course is a reality! What to еxpect in future!" /><published>2018-03-20T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2018-03-20T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/art-forums-first-training-course-reality-%D0%B5xpect-future</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/art-forums-first-training-course-reality-%D0%B5xpect-future/"><![CDATA[<p>Beauty salon Art Forum Hair, Sofia and Albena Atanasova as a lecturer conducted the first training course in February this year. The event was organised by Art Forum – an exclusive importer of 100% natural and high quality human hair and brought together hairdressers interested in the most innovative hairdressing technologies and hair extension methods. Lecturer of the practical part was Albena. She is a talented, dynamic and precise, extremely kind and positive person. For more than 20 years, Albena has been devoted to her profession. For this period she has created many memorable persons (images) from the advertisements and film productions. Over the last 10 years, Albena’s greatest passion are the hair extensions and the wigs. Of course they are always made of natural human hair with the highest quality. Despite of numerous engagements, Albena has been able to hold a training course for people interested in the latest hair extension methods and to share her experience in this area. During the training course almost all topics connected with the hair extensions were discussed. The course included absolutely all steps for hair extensions preparation – from the haircutting methods, stitching of the hair extensions and, of course, the different hair extension methods. One of the main topics is the latest hair extension method – tape-in hair extensions. So far, these are the most sought after hair extensions because they are extremely comfortable and harmless to your hair. Also a very interesting topic was how to care about and maintain our own hair extensions. Don’t miss the chance to join the next training course organised byArt Forum. Further information will be published on the facebook of Art Forum Hair! Challenge yourself to see and try something different entirely in a practical direction! We are looking forward to seeing you!</p>]]></content><author><name>Albena</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Beauty salon Art Forum Hair, Sofia and Albena Atanasova as a lecturer conducted the first training course in February this year. The event was organised by Art Forum – an exclusive importer of 100% natural and high quality human hair and brought together hairdressers interested in the most innovative hairdressing technologies and hair extension methods. Lecturer of the practical part was Albena. She is a talented, dynamic and precise, extremely kind and positive person. For more than 20 years, Albena has been devoted to her profession. For this period she has created many memorable persons (images) from the advertisements and film productions. Over the last 10 years, Albena’s greatest passion are the hair extensions and the wigs. Of course they are always made of natural human hair with the highest quality. Despite of numerous engagements, Albena has been able to hold a training course for people interested in the latest hair extension methods and to share her experience in this area. During the training course almost all topics connected with the hair extensions were discussed. The course included absolutely all steps for hair extensions preparation – from the haircutting methods, stitching of the hair extensions and, of course, the different hair extension methods. One of the main topics is the latest hair extension method – tape-in hair extensions. So far, these are the most sought after hair extensions because they are extremely comfortable and harmless to your hair. Also a very interesting topic was how to care about and maintain our own hair extensions. Don’t miss the chance to join the next training course organised byArt Forum. Further information will be published on the facebook of Art Forum Hair! Challenge yourself to see and try something different entirely in a practical direction! We are looking forward to seeing you!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tape-in Hair Extensions and Our Innovative Technology for Hair Bleaching</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/tape-hair-extensions-innovative-technology-hair-bleaching/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tape-in Hair Extensions and Our Innovative Technology for Hair Bleaching" /><published>2017-12-17T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-12-17T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/tape-hair-extensions-innovative-technology-hair-bleaching</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/tape-hair-extensions-innovative-technology-hair-bleaching/"><![CDATA[<p>The tape-in hair extensions can be used to extend the hair as well as to add extra volume to your own hair. We at Art Forum Hair offer mainly tape-in hair extensions with lengths 50 and 55 cm. Of course, we can also offer you tape-in hair extensions with length and color to your preferences.</p>

<p>How do we achieve a variety of colors?</p>

<p>When we bleach or change the tape-in hair extensions color we again use our own innovative technology for hair bleaching. The method is unique because it keeps the cuticle - the outermost part of the hair shaft. On one hand, this guarantees the strength of the hair and, of course, ensures a much longer life of the hair. With this method it is possible to achieve any desired hair extensions nuance. Very good results have also been obtained with the modern ombre effect. Furthermore, we use only the highest quality virgin human hair.</p>

<p>Our customers have recently pointed out the main advantages of the tape-in hair extensions. They said that the hair is extremely flexible and natural-like.</p>

<ol>
  <li>Flexible</li>
</ol>

<p>The tape-in hair extensions which we offer are extremely flexible compared to the other hair extension methods. One of the reasons for this is that the tape-in hair extensions are put near the base of the hair. Our clients share that they feel comfortable while wearing and brushing their hair. This is also true when they wash and dried their hair. In fact, the maintenance and the care for them are the same as for your own hair.</p>

<ol>
  <li>Natural-like</li>
</ol>

<p>Two main factors are important for the natural-like hair extensions. First, to be made from real human hair and second to have the same color as your own hair. If you truly want flexible and natural-like hair extensions, the tape-in hair extensions are the best solution for you! If you want to check it for yourself, please visit our Art Forum Hair salon!</p>]]></content><author><name>Albena</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tape-in hair extensions can be used to extend the hair as well as to add extra volume to your own hair. We at Art Forum Hair offer mainly tape-in hair extensions with lengths 50 and 55 cm. Of course, we can also offer you tape-in hair extensions with length and color to your preferences.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wedding with hair extensions</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/wedding-hair-extensions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wedding with hair extensions" /><published>2017-06-08T00:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2017-06-08T00:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/wedding-hair-extensions</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/wedding-hair-extensions/"><![CDATA[<p>Every bride desires to look beautiful and irresistible on her wedding day. Hair is one of the details that clearly distinguishes the nice bride from the incredibly beautiful bride. So, the hairstyle for the biggest day of your life is one o the most important things. At the same time, your natural hair not always has the appropriate length, color and density for the glamorous wedding hairstyle. That’s why the hair extensions can help your hair to be longer, fuller and of course to look completely natural. Take a look at our tips for hairstyle on your wedding day!</p>

<h2 id="select-the-best-quality-hair-extensions">Select the best quality hair extensions</h2>

<p>First of all, make sure that you choose the best quality, natural, human hair extensions and go to a hairdresser who has a lot of experience in this field. Altogether, you have to choose the most suitable for you hair extensions - in terms of length, color and quantity of hair. It would be good if the hair salon offers its own assortment of hair extensions and you can purchase and put them in the same place.</p>

<h2 id="which-hair-extension-method-is-the-best-for-you">Which hair extension method is the best for you</h2>

<p>We have already written about the hair extension methods. We at Art Forum Hair always personally approach each of our clients and we can not say which method is best for the wedding hairstyle. However, experience shows that the tape method with sticker is mostly used. It is discreet compared to other methods and can be worn for 2-3 months. The stickers are waterproof and you can swim and walk on a beach during your honeymoon.</p>

<h2 id="when-is-the-best-time-to-put-hair-extensions">When is the best time to put hair extensions?</h2>

<p>The experts recommend at least 2 weeks before the wedding day. This time is enough to get used to your new vision, wedding hair trial and change the hair color if you want. With hair extensions you can have the perfect hairstyle on your most special day!</p>]]></content><author><name>Albena</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every bride desires to look beautiful and irresistible on her wedding day. Hair is one of the details that clearly distinguishes the nice bride from the incredibly beautiful bride. So, the hairstyle for the biggest day of your life is one o the most important things. At the same time, your natural hair not always has the appropriate length, color and density for the glamorous wedding hairstyle. That’s why the hair extensions can help your hair to be longer, fuller and of course to look completely natural. Take a look at our tips for hairstyle on your wedding day!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What are the main human hair extensions types?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/main-human-hair-extensions-types/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What are the main human hair extensions types?" /><published>2017-05-10T00:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2017-05-10T00:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/main-human-hair-extensions-types</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/main-human-hair-extensions-types/"><![CDATA[<p>One of the latest surveys in the beauty industry reports that in the recent years people who want to use hair extensions have increased by more than 40%. At the same time, the human hair extensions are ever increasingly demanded and preferred all over the world. Indeed, natural hair extensions have the same structure as your hair, blend very well with it and their life is much longer than the synthetic ones. There are three basic types of human hair extensions that you can choose from. We will start with the highest quality hair.</p>

<h2 id="virgin-human-hair">Virgin human hair</h2>

<p>Virgin human hair is the best quality hair on the market. This hair is obtained from women or young girls who have never treated their hair chemically (color-dyed) or thermal (curling, straightening) with a curling iron nor a hair straightener. Also, very often this type of hair has not been dried with a hairdryer and it is carefully kept under a headscarf. This is the highest grade hair extension and of course the price is the highest. You can do everything which you do with your own hair - color-dyed, straightening and curling.</p>

<h2 id="remy-human-hair">Remy Human Hair</h2>

<p>Almost all online stores claim that they sell only Remy human hair. What does this mean? When the hair is Ramy all hairs in the extension are arranged in the same order from the top to the root and the hair growth is preserved unchanged. Generally, the remy technology guarantees a longer life of the hair extension and protects the hair from entanglement. The lowest quality human hair follows.</p>

<h2 id="non-remy-human-hair">Non Remy human hair</h2>

<p>Unfortunately, in 90% of the cases the claim that the hair is Remy is an advertisement trick to justify the higher price of the hair. The non Remy hair is usually collected from hairdressing salon’s floors and it is impossible for each hair to be properly arranged (the roots in one direction and the ends in other direction). Very soon the hair extensions get tangled and become practically unusable. We hope we have been useful to you and you could already distinguish the different human hair types!</p>]]></content><author><name>Albena</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the latest surveys in the beauty industry reports that in the recent years people who want to use hair extensions have increased by more than 40%. At the same time, the human hair extensions are ever increasingly demanded and preferred all over the world. Indeed, natural hair extensions have the same structure as your hair, blend very well with it and their life is much longer than the synthetic ones. There are three basic types of human hair extensions that you can choose from. We will start with the highest quality hair.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How to Care for Hair Extensions in the Summer</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/care-hair-extensions-summer/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How to Care for Hair Extensions in the Summer" /><published>2017-04-03T00:00:00+03:00</published><updated>2017-04-03T00:00:00+03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/care-hair-extensions-summer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/care-hair-extensions-summer/"><![CDATA[<p>Оur hair is exposed to stress with the seasons change and the new temperature conditions. The main “stress” factors that influence both our natural hair and the extensions are the harmful UV rays from the sun, the sand on the beach, the salt water of the sea and the chlorine and other chemicals in the swimming pools. So during the summer it is extremely important to care for our hair and to avoid its dryness, thinning and loss of shine. Luckily, there is not much effort required or expensive procedures involved. Our mini program of 3 tips will help you for the beautiful look of your hair extensions during the upcoming hot summer!</p>

<h2 id="avoid-hair-products-with-alcohol">Avoid hair products with alcohol</h2>

<p>Our first tip is to avoid hair styling products that contain alcohol during the summer. These sprays together with the sun will dry your hair further. Although our hair extensions (Art Forum Hair) are made from 100% natural human hair with the highest quality, they do not moisturize as your natural hair from the scalp. Therefore, it is good to use moisturizing hair products with UV protection, hair conditioners and masks that are suitable for your natural hair.</p>

<h2 id="avoid-staying-with-wet-hair-for-long">Avoid staying with wet hair for long</h2>

<p>It is good to dry your hair with a towel after each wash or if it is possible to use a hairdryer. You should not stay long with wet hair. It is advisable to keep your hair braided or in a low bun while swimming in the sea or in the pool to help avoid tangles. Also if you have ceratin bond hair extensions you have to avoid ponytails.</p>

<h2 id="wash-your-hair-after-swimming">Wash your hair after swimming</h2>

<p>During the summer, usually after swimming it is necessary to wash your hair more often. For the high quality hair extensions this is not a problem. You can also use a special extension-friendly brush. It has fiber that slide and do not harm the hair. However, you can use a regular brush to untangle the ends.</p>

<p>As you can see the hair extensions require almost the same care as well as our own in the summer.</p>]]></content><author><name>Albena</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Оur hair is exposed to stress with the seasons change and the new temperature conditions. The main “stress” factors that influence both our natural hair and the extensions are the harmful UV rays from the sun, the sand on the beach, the salt water of the sea and the chlorine and other chemicals in the swimming pools. So during the summer it is extremely important to care for our hair and to avoid its dryness, thinning and loss of shine. Luckily, there is not much effort required or expensive procedures involved. Our mini program of 3 tips will help you for the beautiful look of your hair extensions during the upcoming hot summer!]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">3 Things You should Know Before Getting Extensions</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/things-before-extensions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="3 Things You should Know Before Getting Extensions" /><published>2017-03-23T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-03-23T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/things-before-extensions</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/things-before-extensions/"><![CDATA[<p>Today a lot of ladies, and not only, use hair extensions. The next three practical tips are for those of you who will use hair extensions for the first time.</p>

<h2 id="make-sure-that-your-hairdresser-has-sufficient-experience-with-hair-extensions">Make sure that your hairdresser has sufficient experience with hair extensions</h2>

<p>Recently, almost every second hairdresser puts hair extensions. Though, this does not mean that he or she has sufficient knowledge and experience in this activity. We advise you not to trust the dubious beauty salons with specialists who have watched 5 videos on youtube how to put hair extensions. These hairdressers may not be able to fit them properly. Also, they are not able to advise you which hair color or hair extension methods are the best for you.</p>

<p>For this reason, your first task is to investigate whether your hairdresser has enough experience before you go ahead and accept their advice. You can get such information and recommendation from friends, acquaintances, internet.</p>

<h2 id="only-natural-human-hair">Only natural human hair</h2>

<p>For all of you who want to have beautiful hair and perfect vision it is important to use only 100% natural human hair. Only with this hair you are able to do the same thing such as your natural hair. It can be can color-dyed, curled or straightened. Of course the price for these extensions is high but the hair and the skin are some of the “accessories” which we wear with us every day. That’s why you should not make compromise with the quality.</p>

<h2 id="try-clips-in-extension-first">Try clips-in extension first</h2>

<p>If you want to put hair extensions for the first time, clips-in method is probably the best option for you. As the name suggests this method uses clips (hairpins). With their help the extension is securely attached to your natural hair. Also this method is extremely practical, fast and convenient because the hair can be removed and back attached frequently.</p>

<p><img src="../assets/images/zGPA8959-1024x682.jpg" alt="" /></p>

<p>For more information about our main coiffeur Albena Atanasova, different hair extension methods and everything which you want to know you can see our website artforumhair.com. If you have more questions please contact us at <a href="https://www.facebook.com/artforum.bg/?ref=bookmarks">facebook</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>Albena</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today a lot of ladies, and not only, use hair extensions. The next three practical tips are for those of you who will use hair extensions for the first time.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Main Trends in Hairstyles for 2017</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/main-trends-hairstyles-2017/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Main Trends in Hairstyles for 2017" /><published>2017-03-16T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-03-16T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/main-trends-hairstyles-2017</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/main-trends-hairstyles-2017/"><![CDATA[<p>It is March and the modern trends in the hairstyles for 2017 are available. We review the main and the most popular of them for the year. One thing is sure – simplicity and negligence in the hairstyle are modern. Overall, again the straight and the curly hair are two competing trends.</p>

<h2 id="sleek-straight-hair">Sleek straight hair</h2>

<p>You should use hair straightener because shiny and straight hair will be a hit in 2017. The slogan is the smoother hair, the better. Additionally, you can use liquid crystals and serums to cope with your unruly hair.</p>

<h2 id="curls---from-several-waves-to-curly-hair-like-springs">Curls - from several waves to curly hair like “springs”</h2>

<p>As аn opposite to the sleek and straight hair there is an alternative tendency for curly hair. If you have slightly wavy or curly hair you will be adorable in 2017. Again, use appropriate styling products for curly hair. According to a lot of experts the corkscrew curls look good for several days without special care for them. The curly hair is the perfect trend for all ladies who do not spend much time for their hairstyle.</p>

<h2 id="rapunzels-hair">Rapunzel’s Hair</h2>

<p>The third trend that emerged this year is long hair in all variations and hairstyles. How to achieve this effect?<br />
Do not think that if you eat only fruits and vegetables, wash your hair with quinine shampoo, use hair mask with egg yolk, olive and coconut oil you will have very long hair. All of these Grandma’s recipes have some positive effects but you should be aware that they do not do miracles. The truth is that not everyone’s hair root can nourish hair with a length of 80 cm.</p>

<p>So don’t worry if in you have not cut your hair at all and it is still short. The hair extensions are the best opportunity for you. If you want to see how you will look with long hair just come to our salon at Zlatovrah Street 23. We offer the largest variety of natural Indian hair with the highest quality.</p>]]></content><author><name>Albena</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is March and the modern trends in the hairstyles for 2017 are available. We review the main and the most popular of them for the year. One thing is sure – simplicity and negligence in the hairstyle are modern. Overall, again the straight and the curly hair are two competing trends.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Hair Wigs - Before and Now</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/hair-wigs-now/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Hair Wigs - Before and Now" /><published>2017-03-06T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-03-06T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/hair-wigs-now</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/hair-wigs-now/"><![CDATA[<p>Hair has always been a symbol of beauty and femininity. Since ancient times men and women took a special care of their hair and almost simultaneously started making wigs from different materials - natural human hair, animal fibers, etc. In this respect the history of the fashion and the wigs are inextricably linked with the history of the all humankind. In this article we will do a quick historical overview of the wigs. Finally, we will summarize what significance the wigs have for the modern woman.<!--more--></p>

<p>Ancient Egypt is the place where a lot of beauty treatments are born. Some of them are still applied in the modern world. The Egyptians knew well and used often hair wigs. The women in the Ancient Egypt usually wore black wigs mainly on the ceremonial occasions. To make the wigs flamboyant they decorated them with ornaments of gold and ivory. Wearing a wig has been a real challenge for the body and the spirit taking into account the high temperatures during the day but beauty requires sacrifices…</p>

<p>According to some historical records ancient Greeks colored their hair with red henna. Moreover, the Greeks decorated their hair with flowers. Roman women even colored their hair blond and used bright wigs. They spent a lot of time to prepare their hair and used metal spirals for the curls. Today, a lot of women and men use hair wigs so we could say that they are always fashionable. The reasons for wearing wigs can be divided to modish and healthy. It does not matter if the wigs are made from natural human hair or artificial material the wigs are widely used in the theater and show business. A number of celebrities use wigs just to be more glamorous, unique and even unrecognizable at their stage performances.</p>

<p>In this respect, the hairstylists and the wig-makers of Art Forum Hair are wizards on the topic. We help our customer choose high quality and suiting wig. In our salon you can find natural wigs - different colors and lengths and we can also make a wig according to your preferences, requirements and personal needs.</p>]]></content><author><name>Albena</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hair has always been a symbol of beauty and femininity. Since ancient times men and women took a special care of their hair and almost simultaneously started making wigs from different materials - natural human hair, animal fibers, etc. In this respect the history of the fashion and the wigs are inextricably linked with the history of the all humankind. In this article we will do a quick historical overview of the wigs. Finally, we will summarize what significance the wigs have for the modern woman.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Why Indian Hair is the Best for Extensions?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/indian-hair-best-extensions/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Indian Hair is the Best for Extensions?" /><published>2017-01-29T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-01-29T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/indian-hair-best-extensions</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/indian-hair-best-extensions/"><![CDATA[<p>The Indian hair is the most common type for hair extensions bеcause of the following reasons:</p>

<ul>
  <li>The hair is with medium density and the structure is similar to the European one. Therefore it is very suitable for adding to the European hair.</li>
  <li>It is easily styled and color-dyed. All manipulations are good for a long time.</li>
  <li>It is with dark colors from brown to black and is usually wavy. The curled hair can be maintained or straightened with hair straightener and to be completely smoothed. This is especially important because almost always the natural hair color have to be changed depending on customer preferences who will use the hair. Perhaps only the color of the saturated black hair retained when the extensions are with the same color.</li>
  <li>It is durable. This means that even after cutting, it has a long life. There are many cases when the Indian hair extensions are used around five years.</li>
</ul>

<p>As per the above reasons it can be concluded that the Indian hair is the most suitable replacement for the European hair, especially for people with thick and hard hair. It is also the most in demand for the production of extensions.</p>

<p>On a side note, when we talk about Indian hair we often say that she is a virgin (untreated). What does that mean?</p>

<p>Usually the hair is taken from young Indian girls who have never color-dyed, straightened or curled their hair. It has been also carefully protected from the harmful sun rays. After the cutting, the hair is not processed with anything else except being washed several times with water. Therefore it is possible to have an aroma if it has been treated with essential oils. In some cases, the hair may have single gray or white hairs too.</p>

<p>As a whole, the Indian virgin hair is quite healthy and shiny. Thus it very reacts well to color-dying and has a long life. It can be also conveniently purchased in a variety of conditions - of weight or treces (rows) with different sizes.</p>

<p>That’s why we at Artforum work only with Indian hair!</p>]]></content><author><name>Albena</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Indian hair is the most common type for hair extensions bеcause of the following reasons:]]></summary></entry></feed>